Look, question two:
"When are roadways most slippery?"
(Sheldon:)There are three answers,
none of which are correct.
The correct answer is, "When covered by
liquid sufficient to reduce the coefficient...
...to static friction between the tire
and the road to zero.
(Sheldon:)But not so deep as to introduce
a new source of friction."
(DMV Lady:)Here's your learner's permit. Go away.
(Sheldon:)But I'm not done. I have many
additional concerns about these questions.
- Don't make me climb over this counter.
- All right, come on. Let's go.
WOMAN:
Next.
(Sheldon:)Aced it.
(Howard:)Okay. That's it. Let's boot it up.
(Leonard:)Booting.
(Howard:)This is a state-of-the-art simulator.
(Howard:)I adapted it from something
a friend designed for the Army.
Is that why I appear to be in Fallujah...
(Sheldon:)...behind the wheel
of an up-armored Humvee?
(Howard:)I haven't configured it yet.